<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paper-Conference | YE JIA</title>
    <link>http://localhost:63166/publication_types/paper-conference/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:63166/publication_types/paper-conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Paper-Conference</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:63166/media/icon_hu8220015122150247861.png</url>
      <title>Paper-Conference</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63166/publication_types/paper-conference/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>illumotion: An Optical-illusion-based VR Locomotion Technique for Long-Distance 3D Movement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63166/publication/sin-2024-illumotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63166/publication/sin-2024-illumotion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Locomotion has a marked impact on user experience in VR, but currently, common to-go techniques such as steering and teleportation have their limitations. Particularly, steering is prone to cybersickness, while teleportation trades presence for mitigating cybersickness. Inspired by how we manipulate a picture on a mobile phone, we propose illumotion, an optical-illusion-based method that, we believe, can provide an alternative to these two typical techniques. Instead of zooming in a picture by pinching two ﬁngers, we can move forward by “zooming” toward part of the 3D virtual scene with pinched hands. Not only is the proposed technique easy to use, it also seems to minimize cybersickness to some degree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;illumotion&lt;/em&gt; relies on the manipulation of optics; as such, it requires solving motion parameters in screen space and a model of how we perceive depth. To evaluate it, a comprehensive user study with 66 users was conducted. Results show that, compared with either teleportation, steering or both, illumotion has better performance, presence, usability, user experience and cybersickness alleviation. We believe the result is a clear indication that our novel opticallydriven method is a promising candidate for generalized locomotion.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NivTA: Towards a Naturally Interactable Edu-Metaverse Teaching Assistant for CAVE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63166/upcoming/jia-2024-niv-ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63166/upcoming/jia-2024-niv-ta/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective Collaborative Learning in Edu-Metaverse: A Study on Learners’ Anxiety, Perception, and Behaviour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63166/upcoming/lu-2024-effective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63166/upcoming/lu-2024-effective/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From classroom to metaverse: a study on gamified constructivist teaching in higher education</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63166/publication/ng-2023-classroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63166/publication/ng-2023-classroom/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design of Intelligent Multi-layer Three-dimensional Bicycle Parking Garage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:63166/publication/wang-2020-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:63166/publication/wang-2020-design/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
