<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laura Zhou | YE JIA</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/author/laura-zhou/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/author/laura-zhou/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Laura Zhou</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_218adf0903457e6c.png</url>
      <title>Laura Zhou</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/author/laura-zhou/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enhance Learner Engagement Through Experiential Learning in a Gamified Simulation: a Longitudinal Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/upcoming/icbl_fittslaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/upcoming/icbl_fittslaw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submitted&lt;/strong&gt;: 28th Feb 2025&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Accepted&lt;/strong&gt;: 2nd April 2025&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective Collaborative Learning in Edu-Metaverse: A Study on Learners’ Anxiety, Perception, and Behaviour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/upcoming/lu-2024-effective/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/upcoming/lu-2024-effective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submitted 15 Aug 2024&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accepted&lt;/strong&gt;, 01 Sep 2024&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Abstract&lt;/em&gt; In the evolving landscape of educational technology, Edu-
Metaversepresentsauniquetechnologicalplatformforcollaborativelearn-
ing (CL), which can be especially useful in distance learning settings. Re-
searchers have taken a keen interest in the potential of Edu-Metaverse
for enabling and improving CL; however, the effects of various factors
on CL behaviours and performance still need to be fully understood.
This study used a within-subjects design involving 32 participants (16
females and 16 males) to investigate how learners’ attributes and envi-
ronmental attributes affect CL in Edu-Metaverse. The participants were
randomly assigned to groups of four for a CL session in Edu-Metaverse.
The confirmatory factor analysis revealed that various behavioural met-
rics in Edu-Metaverse mediated the effects of trait anxiety and virtual
space satisfaction on CL performance; perceived understanding of mes-
sages, under the umbrella of social presence, also had a direct effect on
CL performance. These insights underscore the importance of optimising
interactive,perceptual,andsocialcomponentstomakeCLmoreeffective
in Edu-Metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
